晚安 宝贝
Good night, sweatpea.
晚安 亲爱的
Good night, honey.
米奇尔
Mitchell!
咱们的热水浴缸里有个陌生人
There's a stranger in our hot tub!
是谁
Who is it?!
你知道陌生人是什么意思吧
You do know what "stranger" means, don't you?
天啊 我的天啊
Oh, my g -- oh, my god!
他在那儿多久了
How long has he been there?
我在你看到他的前一秒才看到他
I saw him exactly one second before you.
咱俩知道的一样多
You know everything I know.
好吧 我去报警
Okay, I'm -- I'm calling 911.
我去拿我的球棒
I'm getting my bat.
或许我们反应过度了
Maybe we're overreacting.
是啊 他或许有个很好的理由
Yeah, he could have a very good reason for be --
我们至少应该去打个招呼
We should at least say hello.
只是出于礼貌
It's only polite.
好的
Okay.
于是我死死地盯住那只土狼
So I looked that coyote dead in the eye,
我一句话都没说 就让它明白了
and I let him know, without saying a word,
我不会伤害你的
"I will not harm you...
但是我才是这里的老大
but I'm the alpha here".
而它也紧紧地盯着我
And he just stared back at me...
完全被我迷惑住了
mesmerized.
太神奇了
Amazing.
原来 贝瑞刚搬进我们楼上的公寓
Turns out, Barry just moved into the apartment upstairs
他以为这个热水浴盆是全楼公用的
and thought the hot tub was for the whole building.
总而言之 他酷呆了 而且他是直男
Anyway, he's a super-cool guy, and he's straight,
所以没什么好尴尬的
so there's no weirdness.
除了你变成了个十六岁的小姑娘
Aside from you turning into a 16-year-old girl.
我才没呢
I did not.
卡梅隆 把你的手臂给我
Cameron, give me your arm.
好
Okay.
你在做什么
What cha doin'?
我正在学做一名灵气按摩师
Oh, I'm studying to be a reiki master.
我正在把我的正面能量
What I'm doing is I'm transferring my positive energy
传给卡梅隆
into Cameron,
并把他所有的消极能量弄出来
and I'm taking out all the negative energy.
好的
Okay.
-你感觉到了吗 -感觉到了
- Now, do you feel that? - I do.
感觉很温暖吗
Does it feel warm?
确实很温暖
It does.
真的很温暖 米奇尔
It feels warm, Mitchell.
当然暖了 我们可是在泡热水浴呀
Imagine that. In a hot tub.
他开车经过时你准备干吗
What are you gonna do when he drives by?
我要叫他减速
I'm gonna tell him to slow down.
我认为你应该把他从车里拖出来
I think you should drag him out of his car,
然后我们轮流捶他的胃
and we all get turns punching him in the stomach
捶到他吐
until he barfs.
宝贝儿 我想我只会把他的车牌号
Honey, I think I'm just gonna turn over his license plate
交给警察而已
to the police.
拜托
Please.
叫个披萨再打给警察
Order a pizza and call the cops.
看谁到的快点
We'll see who gets here first.
自从他们在奥克蒙特设了减速坎
Ever since they put those speed bumps on Oakmont,
一些驾驶疯狂跑车的司机
some lunatic driver in a crazy sports car
就开始在我们这条街上赛车
has been racing down our street,
这太危险了
and it is dangerous.
我们这里有小孩 还坐婴儿车的婴儿
We've got kids here and babies in strollers
还有喜欢慢跑的妈妈们
and moms who like to jog.
她必须每天跑步 不然会疯掉的
She has to run every day, or she goes crazy.
她就像一条边境牧羊犬
She's like a border collie.
你把我比作一条狗吗
You're comparing me to a dog?
那可是世界上最聪明的狗
The smartest dogs in the world.
你们在干什么呢
What are you guys doing?
做那些警察不肯做的
What the cops won't.
我们在抓那些违章超速驾驶者
We are catching that speeder,
等我们抓到他时 他满耳都会听到这个
and when we do, he's gonna get an earful of this.
开慢点 混蛋
Slow down, jerk!
好了 别激动
Oh! Okay! Easy.
我的天啊 妈 你在干吗
Oh, my god. Mom, what are you doing?
你干吗这么变态
Why are you being such a freak?!
我是出于安全考虑才这么变态的
I am being a freak for safety.
而且我这么做都是为了你们
And I'm doing this for you,
因为我不希望你们发生任何不幸
because I don't want anything bad to happen to you.
这太丢人了
Well, it's embarrassing.
妈 你得找点事干了
Mom, you need a life.
你为什么就不能在博物馆里做做自愿者
Why can't you just volunteer at the museum
或者给那些老人送送布丁呢
or bring pudding to old people?
宝贝儿 要是说有谁丢人的话
Honey, if anybody's being embarrassing right now,
那个人就是你
it's you.
卢克 我是你老爸
Luke, I am your father!
这让我想起了在产房的时候
That takes me back to the delivery room.
当你从你妈的私处钻出来时
That's what I said to you
我就是这么跟你说的
when you were coming out of your mom's lady parts.
天啊 老爸
Oh, my god, dad!
我的天 我认识那俩女生
Oh, my god. I know those girls.
- 怎么了 你觉得我们丢人吗 - 是的
- What? Are you ashamed of us? - Yes!
《甜蜜高谷》咯
Ooh. Sweet Valley High!
是那个住在第七街的女人打来的
This is that woman from the house on seventh street!
好极了
Oh, good!
是啊 如果我在下个月底前把房子卖出去
Yeah, if I sell it by the end of next month,
我就能打败盖尔·索普 成为季度最佳销售员了
I dethrone Gil Thorpe as salesman of the quarter.
太棒了 爸
That's awesome, dad.
确实棒极了
It is awesome.
我是菲尔·邓菲
Phil Dunphy.
超速驾驶的家伙来了 超速驾驶的家伙来了
That's the speeder! That's the speeder!
开慢点 混蛋 开慢点
Slow down, jerk! Slow down!
是的 不 是的 这太好了
Yeah. No. Yeah, that's great.
好的 尽管问
Okay, fire away.
-2urn801 -好的 给我地址就行
- 2-u-r-n-8-0-1. - Yeah. Oh, uh, just the address.
-好的 一 零 -801 2urn 笔呢
- Yep. Okay. 1-0... - 8-0-1. 2-u-r-n. A pen.
-一 北边 第七 -我给爸了
- 1...North...Seventh... - I gave it to dad.
-ur -街
- U-r... - ...Street.
-我的天 -好的 10-4
- Oh, god. - Okay. 10-4.
这将是我自2006年以来我最走运的一年
This is gonna be my best year since 2006.
走吧 孩子 该送你去学校了
Let's go, kid. Back to the salt mine.
不用了 杰 我今天骑自行车去上学
That's okay, Jay. I'm biking to school today.
你真行
Good for you.
学校里有一群很酷的小孩
There's a bunch of cool kids
每天都骑自行车上学
who ride their bikes every day.
我也想骑
Thought I'd join them.
等等 等等 等等 等等
Hey, wait. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
那是什么鬼东西
What the hell is that?
我的新自行车 妈妈昨天给我买的
My new bike. Mom got it for me yesterday.
很周到吧
Pretty sweet, huh?
辅助轮
Training wheels?
质量很好的 还是订做的
Nice ones. Custom made.
这种型号的自行车一般都不配辅助轮的
They don't usually come on bikes this size.
-歌洛莉亚 -怎么了
- Gloria! - What's wrong?
你不会骑自行车吗
You don't know how to ride a bike?
我会骑这辆自行车
I know how to ride this bike.
这辆车连斯蒂芬·霍金[肌肉萎缩的物理学家]都会骑
Stephen Hawking could ride that bike.
我来了 怎么了
Ay. What happened?
他摔倒了吗
Did he fall?
怎么可能摔倒
How could he fall?
你不能让他骑
You can't send him to school
带辅助轮的自行车去上学
on a bike with training wheels.
同学们会笑他的
They'll make fun of him.
你没有教他怎么骑自行车吗
Didn't you teach him how to ride a bike?
怎么教 我自己都不会骑自行车
How could I? I don't know how to ride a bike.
十亿中国人都会做的事
2/3 of my house can't do
我们家居然有三分之二的人都不会
what a billion Chinese do.
我妈觉得骑自行车很危险
My mother thought that riding a bike was dangerous.
她会说 "别人就会这样把你抓走的"
She would say, "that's how people grab you"!
好吧 这样好了
Okay, this is how it's going down.
今天 我开车带你去学校
Today I'm driving you to school,
周末 我也给你买辆自行车
on the weekend, I'm buying you a bike,
我来教你们俩骑车
and I'm teaching both of you.
我很紧张
I'm nervous...
但也很兴奋
but I'm excited.
你们俩个去玩吧 我就免了
You two have fun. I pass.
这根本不合理
It makes no sense.
那个东西怎么可能立得住
There's no reason that thing should stay upright.
你也不可能立得住
There's no reason you should stay upright,
但事实就是可以
but it just works.
菲尔 快进来
Hey, Phil. Come on in.
劳拉 你好呀
Laura, good day.
我超喜欢门口的设计
Well, I couldn't love this entry any more.
很有家的感觉
It's very welcoming.
我十分钟后还有点事要办
Yeah, I got a thing in 10 minutes,
-所以我要快点搞掂这件事 -没问题
- so I have to make this quick. - Great.
让我给你介绍一下
Um, let me run through
我的销售三策略
my three-pronged approach to selling --
我只需要一个策略 那就是把房子卖出去
I only need one prong -- sell the house.
我不想跟那个女的一样
I don't want to be that yutz
把房子的价位定的太高
who prices her house too high
结果一整年都卖不出去
so it sits around for a year
而那些在星期天无所事事的人
while every lookie-loo without something to do on Sundays
都跑来看我的房子 窥探我的隐私
is going through my underwear drawer.
佣金是多少
What's the number?
我们需要考虑几个因素
Well, there are quite a few factors to take into --
我只要一个数字
Need a number.
我们规定的佣金是百分之一点四
Uh, we list at 1.4.
底线是百分之一点二五
We take anything north of 1.25.
成交
Done!
好极了
Great!
我文件都准备好了 现在就能签
I got all the paperwork right here.
别急 想要跟我进一步发展
Whoa, whoa, whoa. You got to buy me a beer
怎么也得先把我灌醉才行
before you can put your hand up my sweater.
我可没有那种冒犯之意
Oh, I had no intention --
要是这周末开放日举行的成功
Put on a great open house this weekend,
零头就都是你的
the listing's yours.
放马过来吧 劳拉
Bring it, Laura.
想要考验我 我可是久经考验的
You want to test me? I've been tested my whole life.
别人到头来怎么输的都不知道
They could never find anything.
那么星期天中午十二点到下午四点来举行开放日如何
So, uh, Sunday 12:00 to 4:00 for the open house?
-这时间合适吗 -很好
- That works for you? - Great.
好的 如果你还有什么问题
Great. Oh, and if you have any questions
或是什么需要 打我电话就行了
or you need anything, just call.
跟我合作就像和朋友合作一样愉快
When you work with me, you're working with a friend.
你真体贴 我很喜欢你
That is so sweet. I like you.
别让我失望 别到最后逼我炒了你
God, I hope I don't have to fire you.
你好 我是克莱尔 请留言
Hi. This is Claire. Leave a message.
亲爱的 是我
Hey, honey. It's me.
我刚开完会
I just finished the meeting,
她简直是完美客户
and she is the perfect client.
对价格不怎么计较
Realistic about the price...
只想尽快把房子卖出去 她个性也很率真
she wants to sell fast, and she's a real character.
你真应该见见她
You got to...meet her.
不过她就快搬走了 我看还是算了吧
But she's moving soon, so what's the point?
你加班加到真晚
Wow, you worked late.
是啊 难熬的一天 我只想马上坐下歇歇
Yes. Brutal day. I just want to sit.
正好 莉莉睡着了
Perfect. Lily's asleep.
贝瑞待会跟咱们一起泡热水浴
Barry's meeting us in the hot tub.
要是你压力太大
If you're feeling stressed,
他可以给你灵气按摩一下
he could give you a treatment.
我看还是算了吧
Ah, that's all right.
我明天约了赤脚医生
I have an appointment with Dr. Bigfoot tomorrow.
好了好了 又来了
Okay. Here comes the judge.
灵气按摩什么的都是骗人的 小卡
Reiki is a bunch of nonsense, Cam.
那人就是个疯子
That guy is a nut.
你每次都这样
You do this every time.
每当我们结识一个新朋友
We meet a new friend,
只要他们说出一件你不喜欢的事
they say one thing you don't like,
你就会无情的把他们踢出局
and you just write 'em off.
我哪有
I do not!
没有吗 你忘了那个"但是可是雷切尔"了
Oh, really? What about "but yet Rachel"?
我很想去 但是可是 我不怎么喜欢逛公园
"I'd love to go, but yet, I don't feel like parking".
要不就说"但是" 要不就说"可是"
It's either "but" or "yet",
没有放在一块说的
not both.
你该庆幸到目前为止还没人来教训你
You're lucky no one's kicked your butt yet.
那托马斯又怎么说
What about Thomas?
你把他踢出局就是因为
You wrote him off because
他先上主菜 后上沙拉
he serves the salad after the meal,
顺便说一句 这在欧洲是很正常的
which, by the way, is very common in Europe.
他是从欧洲哪来的 自命不凡斯坦国吗
What part of Europe is he from? Pretentious-stan?
好吧
Okay, fine.
继续指责吧 别交任何朋友
Keep judging. Don't let anyone in.
我也可以少管点
I could care less.
你是想说你才懒得管呢吧
I think you mean you couldn't care less,
因为你要说"可以少管点"
because if you could care less,
就证明你还是管了
that means that you care a little bit.
好吧 我要去泡热水浴了
All right. I'm going to the hot tub.
要是我在这里多待一分钟
If I stay in here one more minute,
我的头就真的要爆了
my head is literally gonna explode.
我希望不会 因为要是真的会爆的话
Well, I hope not, because if you mean "literally" --
我待在自己家里都没有安全感
I don't feel safe in my own home!
菲尔 亲爱的 帮我一把
Phil, honey, I need your help.
帮你干吗
With what?
什么东西是违章超速者无法躲开的
What is the one thing a speeder can't outrun?
子弹 激光
Ooh. Bullets. A laser.
我知道了 大炮 老爸 快帮我想想
Oh, I know -- a falcon! Dad, jump in.
时机不对
Not a good time.
-雷射炮 -这个给力
- A laser falcon! - That's awesome.
答案是 羞愧感
Shame.
"使你的邻居们变得迟钝"
"Slow down your neighbors"!?
不是这个意思 "放慢速度"
No. "Slow down" --
是对违章超速者说的
talking to the speeder --
是谁要对那违章超速者说呢
Who's talking to the speeder?
你的邻居们
Your neighbors.
才不是这个意思呢
It doesn't say that.
没错 那上面只写着"使你的邻居们变得迟钝"
Yeah, it just says "Slow down your neighbors"!
-菲尔 -我懂你想表达什么
- Phil. - I know what you were going for,
可你那标牌上写的就是"使你的邻居们变得迟钝"
but now all I can see is "slow down your neighbors"!
你们都错了 因为这再清楚不过了
Well, you're all wrong, 'cause this is incredibly clear.
而且这很重要
And it's really important.
我们需要在街区贴满这些告示
We need to put these signs up all over the neighborhood.
这可不像你啊 这是胆小鬼做的事
I don't know. It seems kind of cowardly.
为什么不直接打匿名电话给警方呢
Why don't you just make an anonymous call to the police?
我老早打过了 可他们什么忙都帮不上
I called the police, and they were totally unhelpful.
我早就说啦
Surprise. Surprise.
菲尔 你到底站不站在我这边
Phil, come on. Are you with me or not?
我当然站在你这边
Of course I'm with you.
不然呢 难道站在那人这边
Who else would I be with? This guy?
我和那人又没有任何瓜葛
I have no connection to this guy.
-很好 帮我把它贴出去 -不
- Good! - No!
好吧
Fine.
在你炮轰我之前 我要说
Before you judge me,
我已经整整七个季度
I have come in second to Gil Thorpe
都在季度最佳销售员的评比上输给盖尔·索普而位居第二
for salesman of the quarter seven quarters in a row.
整整七个季度
Seven.
没人会记得第二名是谁
Nobody remembers second best.
人人都爱迈克尔·乔丹
Oh, yeah, everybody loves Michael Jordan,
可有谁会想起斯科蒂·皮蓬
but nobody thinks of Scottie Pippen.
我会记得他的唯一原因是
The only reason I remember him
他跟我最爱的音乐剧同名
is because he's named after my favorite musical.
-米奇 -是贝瑞啊
- Oh, hey, Mitch. - Hey. It's Barry.
我只是来通知你们
Uh, I just want to let you guys know
你们有一个自动洒水器在漏水
you got a sprinkler head that's leaking out there.
谢谢你 贝瑞 我会通知园丁的
Oh. Thanks, Barry. I'll let the gardener know.
好的 又或者我可以朝它舞动一下我的双手
All right. Or maybe I could just wave my hands over it
用我的灵气修好它
and heal it that way.
只是玩笑
I'm joking.
天呐 差点被你骗到
Oh, god. That was a good one.
听着 不用担心
Look, don't worry about it.
我看得出来 只要我一开始谈灵气
As soon as I started talking about reiki,
你就觉得我的精神也许有点不太正常
I could tell you thought I might be a little nutty.
有这么明显吗
Was I that obvious?
你整天都冲我翻白眼
You roll your eyes a lot.
给你说中了
Uh, no, it's true.
我的确爱翻白眼
It's true, no.
我曾经看到一张自己
I-I once saw a picture of myself
在朋友的诵诗比赛上拍的照片
at a friend's poetry slam,
结果照片里能看到的只有我的眼白
and all you could see were the whites of my eyes.
我看上去就像孤女安妮
Yeah, I looked like Little Orphan Annie.
那部动画片
The cartoon.
总而言之 如有冒犯之处我很抱歉
Anyway, I'm sorry if I offended you.
别 不用道歉
No. Don't apologize.
唯一会让我觉得有所冒犯的事
Look, I -- only thing that offends me
就是一个不能无法面对真实的自己的人
is a man who doesn't live in his own truth.
而且我知道你现在正很努力地
And I appreciate how hard you're trying
不去翻白眼 我为此表示感谢
not to roll your eyes right now.
因为我就快晕过去了
'Cause I'm about to pass out!
我看出来了
I see it.
我准备好了
Okay! I'm ready!
他穿了些什么东西
What the hell's he wearing?
保护软垫 还得再加点吗
Protection pads. He needs more?
我们只是学骑车而已 又不是训练警犬
We're riding bikes. We're not training police dogs.
好了 孩子 过来 上来吧
All right, kid. Come on. Get on.
上车
On board.
好样的
Attaboy.
好了 准备好了吗
All right, we ready?
骑
Ride!
小心点 小乖乖
Be careful, papi.
别理她
Ignore her.
那孩子连在机场的
I've seen the kid fall down
自动人行道上都能摔跤
on that moving sidewalk at the airport,
所以我没抱太大希望
so I didn't have high hopes.
可谁能会到呢 那孩子天生是个骑车的料
But what do you know? The kid was a natural.
妈妈 这太简单了
Mom! It's so easy!
太棒了 曼尼
Bravo, Manny!
我就跟你说嘛
I told you!
小心地上的坑
Be careful with the bump!
等等 那人是谁
Hey, wait a minute. Who's that guy?
杰 他会抓走曼尼的
Jay, he's gonna grab him!
没人会被抓走 那只是个邻居而已
Oh, no one's grabbing anyone. It's a neighbor.
可歌洛莉亚
Gloria, on the other hand,
简直是个天生的悲剧
was a natural disaster.
在骑车之前你要先做三件事
There are three things you want to do before you ride.
曼尼说
Manny.
检查鞋带 调整后视镜
Check your shoelaces, adjust your mirror,
还有测试车铃
and test your bell.
好的 鞋带系好了
Okay. Shoelaces tied...
后视镜视野不错
the mirror is good...
车铃也很正常
...the bell is ringing.
好了 然后呢
Okay, now what?
骑啊
Ride.
别别别 杰
Ay, no, no, no, Jay.
别推我 我可不想受伤
Don't push me! I don't want to get hurt!
相信我 不会让你受伤的
Trust me. I'm not gonna hurt you.
你就像一幅名画
You're a work of art.
要是被划伤
If you get scratched,
那可就掉价了
the value goes down.
我是为了缓和气氛搞笑一下
I'm making a joke to lighten the mood.
一点都不好笑
It's not working!
你就骑吧
Let's just do this.
好吧
Okay.
慢点
Slowly.
杰 慢点啊
Jay, slowly.
放松 你摔不了
Relax. You're not gonna fall.
我抓着你呢 把脚放在踏板上
I got you. Put your feet on the pedals.
眼睛看着路
Now look where you're going.
看着路啊
Look where you're going!
不 我要摔了 我要摔了
No, I'm falling. I'm falling.
目视前方 去吧去吧
Look straight ahead. Go, go, go.
-踩踏板 -不要 杰
- Pedal! - No, Jay!
你一个劲儿按铃干吗
What are you ringing the bell for?
你怎么能放手呢 杰
Ay! Why you let me go, Jay?!
不对不对 踩踏板
No, no! Pedal!
目视前方 看着路
Look where you're going! Look where you're going!
我要宰了你 杰
I'm gonna kill you, Jay!
好了 今天学得不错
Okay. Good day's work.
我们去珠宝店逛逛怎么样
What do you say we hit the jewelry store?
菲尔
Phil?
劳拉
Laura!
你在干吗
What are you doing?
把这个告示牌 拆下来
Taking this...sign down!
我发现上面写着你的车牌号
I recognized your license plate.
这也太荒唐了
This is ridiculous!
我知道 整个小区都贴满了告示牌
I know. They're all over the neighborhood.
什么疯子会干这种蠢事
What kind of lunatic does something like this?
谁知道呀
Who knows?
也许是某个无所事事的家庭主妇
It's probably some bored housewife
对丈夫无爱 对生活怨恨
who hates her husband and hates her life,
于是就把气撒在其他人身上
so she takes it out on the rest of us!
要么就是家里太平无事
Or things are so good at home,
所以她就出门来找茬
she's out looking for problems.
相信我
Trust me.
这种女人绝对是欲求不满
This woman needs to get laid.
我觉得不是这个原因
I don't think that's the issue.
拿着 把这个贴上
Here. Stick this up.
这是老娘留给她的口信
Send her a message from me.
好的
Okay.
天啊
Oh, my gosh.
我的告示牌怎么成这样了
What happened to my sign?
不知道啊
I don't know!
我把它钉好后就走开了
I put it up, I went away,
等我回来时 就已经成两半了
I came back -- it was in pieces!
这也太疯狂了
This is so crazy.
是疯狂啊
Crazy!!
克莱尔 这件事本身就是疯狂的
Claire, this whole thing is crazy.
也许我们应该作出点让步
Maybe we should back off a little bit.
菲尔 绝不
You know what, Phil? No.
我才不让步
I am not gonna back off.
知道吗 我这么做是为了咱们街区居民的安全
Okay? I am doing this for the safety of our neighborhood.
这是怎么回事啊
Well, what's going on here?
小卡
Hey, Cam.
我正在用内功清除他体内的负面能量
Just getting rid of some negative energy.
估计你得清到周二 等你清完我们再回来
Oh, well, in that case, we'll be back Tuesday.
米奇 你已经没事了
You're all set, Mitch.
贝瑞
Barry.
-伙计 感觉真舒服啊 -是吧
- Oh, man, that was -- that was great. - Yeah?
别忘了合十礼 伙计
Namaste, man.
-阿弥陀佛 -阿弥陀佛
- Namaste. - Namaste.
好了 我不打扰你们了
All right. I'm gonna get out of your hair.
我去洗个快澡
I'm gonna grab a quick tub
再看看能不能弄点吃的
and see if I can rustle up some food.
不 别弄了
Oh, no. Hey, don't rustle.
我们今晚开伙 你过来一起吃吧
We're making dinner tonight. You're coming.
是啊 来吧
Yeah, come down.
-这样好吗 -当然了
- Yeah? - Yes.
谢谢你 米奇
Thank you, Mitch.
看见没 已经见效了
See? It's working already.
阿弥陀佛
Namaste.
你想说什么
What?
你知道我要说什么
You know what I'm looking for.
-他人很好 -不是这句
- He's a very nice guy. - That's not it.
抱歉 我之前的判断有点仓促
I'm sorry I made a snap judgment.
也不是这个哦
Still not it.
你是对的
You were right.
这就对了
There she is.
米奇尔 你好
Hello, Mitchell.
高太太 我是卡梅隆
Oh. Mrs. Ko. I'm Cameron.
米奇尔的娇妻
Mitchell's the other one.
你来这有事吗
What are you doing here?
我刚带人去看了楼上的公寓
I just finished showing the apartment upstairs.
什么意思 那贝瑞呢
What do you mean? What about Barry?
贝瑞是谁
Who's Barry?
新来的房客
The new tenant.
里面没人住 这是间空房
Nobody living up there. It's empty.
-可是 -你要是看见楼上有人就打我电话
- But... - You see anybody up there, you call me.
是我丈夫
My husband.
我来了
I'm coming!
你该庆幸法律不让你俩结婚
You two so lucky they don't let you get married.
这不是我的问题
The problem wasn't me.
都怪杰 他教得也太烂了
It was Jay. He's a very bad teacher.
太霸道了
Very bossy.
人家不喜欢那样嘛
I don't respond to that.
我喜欢有绅士风度 关爱有加的人
I need somebody gentle, nurturing,
要像女性一样温柔
like a woman.
歌洛莉亚 你好吗
Hey. Gloria. What's up?
你能教我骑自行车吗
Can you teach me how to ride a bike?
你竟然不会骑车
You can't ride a bike?
惹人怜爱啊
I love that about you.
我一直觉得你完美无缺呢
I was beginning to think you didn't have any flaws.
听着 我很想教你
Listen, I wish I could,
不过我约人看房要迟到了
but I'm late for an open house.
我可以教你
I could teach you.
-真的吗 -当然了
- Really? - Sure.
我可是单车帝
I'm a great bike rider.
我教过好多朋友呢
I've taught a bunch of my friends.
我从没教过别人任何东西
I never taught anyone anything.
但我被人放了鸽子 正闲得慌呢
But my playdate canceled, so I was wide open.
贝瑞
Barry?
在
Yep!
是你啊 卡梅隆
Oh. Hey, Cameron.
你在里面干吗
What are you doing in there?
我只是整理一下
I'm just tidying up a little bit.
怎么了
What's up?
你住在我女儿的公主城堡里吗
Are you living in our daughter's princess castle?!
什么
What?!
少来了 别开玩笑了
No, don't be ridiculous.
我住在这儿 兄弟
I'm living in here, man.
只是睡在那里面
I'm sleeping in there.
你说你刚搬到楼上
You said you had just moved in upstairs.
不 我是说我刚搬过来
No, I said I just moved in.
对不起 我以为这暗示了
I'm -- I'm sorry. I thought it was implied...
暗示你住在玩具屋里
that you're living in a dollhouse?
好了 咱别在大庭广众之下的说这个了
Okay. Let's not do this outside.
好吗
All right?
要不要到屋里去
You want to go inside
以成人的方式讨论这个问题
and talk about this like two adults?
好的 就这样吧
Yes. Let's do that.
好
Great.
不
No --
-不是这间屋 -没关系 我刚打扫过
- No! - It's okay. I just cleaned up.
快进来
Come on in.
天哪 你还真住在这里面
Oh, my God! You are living in here!
进来再说
Inside voices.
贝瑞
Barry.
你是不是无家可归
Are you homeless?
无家可归
Homeless?
你疯了吗
Are you insane?
看看这里 你看
Look at this place.I mean...
好吧 没想到我不得不说出这种话
Okay. I can't even believe I'm having to say this,
不过 你不能住在这
but you can't -- you can't stay here.
兄弟
Oh, boy.
是不是因为
This is about the --
我帮米奇尔做内功排毒那件事
the body work I did with Mitchell, isn't it?
要是你因此觉得不爽的话
'Cause I would understand if that was...
我可以理解
bothering you.
不是 而是因为你居然住在小女孩的玩具屋里
No. You are living in a little girl's toy,
所以你必须搬出去
and you have to move out.
好吧 但这着实会让晚宴变的很尴尬
Okay, well, this is gonna make dinner really awkward.
没有晚宴 晚宴取消了
There's no dinner! Dinner is off!
明白了吗 快点 走吧
Okay? Now, come on. Let's go.
不 不 不 别碰我 我不喜欢别人碰我
No, no, no. Don't touch me. I don't like to be touched.
可你是个按摩师啊
You're a massage therapist.
我是灵气大师 基本不需要触碰
I'm a reiki master. Very little touching.
好吧 贝瑞 听我说
Okay, Barry. Listen to me.
你说
Okay.
你是个好人
You're a very nice man.
我和米奇尔都很喜欢你
Mitchell and I like you very much.
谢谢
Thank you.
但我 不客气
But I'm -- you're welcome.
我要抓着你的手
I'm going to take your hand...
我就要抓
Yes, I am.
别像盯野狼一样盯我看 我又不是犬科动物
Don't give me the coyote look. I'm not a canine.
我们一起离开这里
We're gonna walk out of here together.
没人会伤害你
Nobody's gonna hurt you.
你这样做不会有好结果的
Oh, this is not gonna end very well.
把手给我
Give me your hand.
小卡
Cam?!
米奇尔 快报警
Mitchell! Call 911!
怎么了
What's happening?!
贝瑞是个疯子
Barry's a nut!
他一直住在莉莉的城堡里
He's been living in Lily's castle!
什么
What?
你好啊 米奇尔
Hey, Mitchell!
上帝啊 我还以为他住在楼上呢
Oh, my god! I thought he was living upstairs!
快去报警就是了
Just call the police!
你想让我停下来把整件事讲给你听吗
Do you want me to stop and give you the whole story?!
我从没 我从没说过我住楼上
I never -- I never said upstairs.
米奇尔
Mitchell!
快报警 别掐我
Call 911! Stop pinching!
好吧 顺便跟你说
Okay. And just for the record,
我是对的
I was right!
我还是觉得你不应该对别人评头论足
I still don't think you should judge people!
我说放开我
I said get off me!
好吧 歌洛莉亚
Okay, Gloria.
是什么让你害怕骑车
What scares you about riding a bike?
失去控制然后跌倒
Losing control and falling down.
很好 还有吗
Great. What else?
怕有人把我抓走
Somebody grabbing me?
真怪异的想法 还有吗
That's weird. What else?
-看上去很傻 -好吧
- Looking foolish. - Okay.
你看 你就是被这些消极的想法牵绊住了
See, all these bad thoughts are holding you back.
那我们怎么才能摆脱那些消极的想法呢
So how do we get rid of these bad thoughts?
把他们射出来
We shoot 'em out!
不要 你敢
No, don't you dare!
快骑
Ride!
你敢
Don't you dare!
-快骑 -卢克 快停下
- Ride! - Luke, stop it!
-不要 -我说快骑
- No! - I said ride!
不要 不要
No, no!
-快骑 -我要找你妈告状
- Ride! - I'm gonna tell your mother!
说什么 说你在骑车吗
What? That you're riding a bike?
不是 是说你
No, that you're...
太棒了 我会骑车了
Yes! I'm riding the bike!
那是世界上最棒的感觉了
It was the greatest feeling in the world.
卢克是对的
Luke was right.
没有什么可害怕的
There was nothing to be afraid of.
下车 下车
Get off the bike! Get off the bike!
-把车给我 给我 -别抓我
- Give it to me! Give it to me! - Ay, don't grab me!
不 不 不 别抓我
No, no! No, don't grab me!
走开 走开 走开
Go, go, go, go, go! Go!
鞋带 后视镜
Laces, mirror...
车铃
bell.
减速 你个混蛋
Slow down, jerk!
感谢二位的光临 很高兴认识你们
Thanks so much for coming. It was great to meet you both.
祝你们一切顺利
Have a good one!
再见
See you later.
进展怎么样
How's it going?
很好 来了很多人
Hey, great. Lots of people.
听着 我在想那些标志的事
Listen, I was thinking about those signs.
使你的邻居们变得迟钝
"Slow down your neighbors"!
事实上 我觉得那个标示的意思是
Oh, actually, I think they meant
"减速" 是对你说的
"slow down" -- talking to you --
谁说的呢 "你的邻居们"
Who's talking? "Your neighbors".
随便了
Anyway...
你觉不觉得
Yeah, um, you think maybe it's possible
你在居民区
that you do drive a little too fast
开得有点太快了
in a residential neighborhood
这周围还有孩子 也许
with children present, maybe, or...
菲尔 我很感谢你的关心
Oh, Phil, I appreciate your concern,
但是问题不在我
but I am not the problem.
而是那个写标示的疯婆子
It's the crazy sign lady
她连个完整的句子都不会写
who can't put a sentence together --
那才是你该解决的问题
that's your problem.
菲尔 亲爱的
Phil? Honey?
克莱尔
Claire?
上帝啊
Ohh. God.
我得喝点水
I had to get some water.
我在追那个疯子
I was chasing that crazy maniac.
差一点就追上了
I got so close.
然后你就这么放弃了
And you just gave up?
那可不是我所认识的克莱尔
That's not the Claire that I know.
-快出去继续追呀 -真的假的
- Get back out there! - Really?
当然了
Yeah!
菲尔 我把手机落在药房了
Phil, I left my phone at the drugstore.
-我一会儿就回来 -好的 待会见
- I'll be right back. - Okay, bye.
你好 我是克莱尔·邓菲
Hey. Hi. I'm Claire Dunphy.
菲尔的妻子
I'm Phil's wife.
别拉着她说了
Let's not talk her ear off.
她该走了
She's got to go.
我是劳拉 很高兴认识你
I'm Laura. Nice to meet you.
这房子真漂亮
Oh, beautiful house.
谢谢
Thanks.
你会经过格林利夫吗
Hey, are you going by Greenleaf?
会
Actually, yeah.
我刚才骑车骑得太累了
I just overdid it on my bike,
现在没劲骑回去了
and I cannot get back on there.
没问题 我载你一程
No problem. I'll give you a ride.
这主意太糟了
That's a terrible idea.
-为什么 -为什么
- Why? - Why?
我这希望我是那种
I wish I were one of those people
热爱双重身份所带来的刺激感的人
who thrives on the danger of leading a double life.
就像是布鲁斯·韦恩
You know, Bruce Wayne,
彼得·帕克
Peter Parker,
汉娜·蒙塔那
Hannah Montana.
那个主意 太糟了
That's a terrible...idea,
因为你的自行车还在这呢
because your bike is here.
你准备怎么办 就把车丢在这 那太失礼了
What are you gonna do? Leave it? That's rude!
那随时过来拿就好了
Oh, just pick it up whenever.
随时 什么是随时
Whenever?! What's "whenever"?
那也太随意了
That's so open-ended.
行了 别叫唤了
Oh, stop it.
走吧 克莱尔 咱们走
Come on, Claire. Let's fly.
我喜欢她这么活力四射
Ahh. I love her energy.
我来啦
I'm coming!
你为什么要搬走
So, why do you want to move?
我想住在有门卫的大厦里
Ah, I want a high-rise with a doorman.
再说 这个小区有点疯狂
Besides, this neighborhood is getting a little crazy.
感同身受呀
Oh, tell me about it.
有个疯子
There's this one whack job...
不用再多说了
You know, don't say another word.
我敢说我知道你要说的是谁
I bet I know exactly who you're thinking of.
克莱尔气得要死
Claire was furious.
她说我从各个角度都背叛了她
She said I betrayed her on every level.
所以我打电话给花店
So, I called the florist,
订了一打气球
and I have ordered one dozen mylar balloons.
看你还能气多久 亲爱的
Good luck staying mad, honey.
快点 是那个文明社会发明了字母表
Come on, which civilization invent the alphabet
我不知道
I don't know.
你知道的
Yes, you do.
这个问题我们都复习了上百遍了
We've been over this a hundred times.
老爸 让我来 我是个很厉害的老师
Allow me, dad. I'm a great teacher.
谁发明了字母表
Who invented the alphabet?
我 不 知 道
I...don't...know.
卢克
Luke!
我浑身都湿了 你干吗呀
I got soaked! What are you doing?!
说呀 说呀
Say it! Say it!
卢克 别闹了
Luke, that's enough!
我的天呐
Oh, my god!
我不知道 我不知道 我不知道
I don't know! I don't know! I don't know!
是腓尼基人 是腓尼基人
The Phoenicians! The Phoenicians!
答案 正确
That's...right.
本年度最杰出的老师
Teacher of the year.
我把她交给你了 兄弟
She's all yours, buddy.